i will be in charm city on wednesday december 3rd now i know there's been some confusion with
the rsvps and whatnot you should have gotten a confirmation email and then a re-confirmation
if none of that happened and you know that you rsvp just come through also want to remind you
even if you didn't rsvp and you like i'm just now finding out we are absolutely allowing folks to
come in at 7 p.m after the book talk to still be a part of the meet and greet and book signing and
let me tell you what i love about when i do stuff is that it don't just be dope because i'm there
it be dope because of where we be at so shout out to charm city cultural cultivation headquarters and
derrick adams for hosting me and because of y'all like the community that i've built over the years
has just been so dope and it continues to grow and evolve and uh expand mentally intellectually
compassionately all the things so come through i will see you all on wednesday december 3rd
for the actual book talk we'll be there at 5 30 if you're coming through to get your book signed and
do a meet and greet come on at 7 p.m and i've seen some of y'all been half naked in the polar vortex
still trying to get in the club i done seem to like a 27 inch zenith believe it so i hope whatever
weather goes on it doesn't stop you from coming through to get some knowledge did i got lipstick
on my teeth damn it was on there the whole time
you